One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The Execution Platform
Yeah! Ace is alive!
Hey, stay with me!
Was that Ace's brother?!
Look at this!
I almost passed out!
Like Pops and Red Hair
he used Conqueror's Haki!
Was he the one who did it?
Seems like he used it unconsciously.
I didn't know that he had
such tremendous power!
He was born with it as I thought!
He uses it, too!
Back down if your heart is weak!
He is not just another rookie!
Conqueror's Haki!
But it's not surprising because he's
the son of Dragon the revolutionary!
Vice Admiral Doberman!
Hey, where did you get the power from?!
Huh?! What power?!
Never mind!
He's not aware of it!
So it's not ready to be used!
But it's no wonder that he attracts people!
This is why they say "blood will tell," Dragon!
Don't let him escape this battlefield! If
you do, he'll prove a formidable foe for us!
Make sure he dies!
Let's get Whitebeard first!
He's a monster but he's wounded
badly! Bring him down at any cost!
You guys!
Pops?!
From now on, back Straw Hat Luffy up...
with all your strength!
Ace's brother?!
Straw Hat-boy! Watch out!
You're...
the allied pirate of Whitebeard, Bohemian Knight Doma!
Nice to meet you, Vice Admiral Momonga!
DeCalvan Brothers!
You got to fight...!
Against us!
Thunder Lord McGuy!
I need you to fight me,
Vice Admiral Doberman!
I-Is this...?!
We pirates from the New World will assist you!
Ace-chan's right there! Let's go, Straw Hat!
The allied pirates of Whitebeard
are surrounding Straw Hat!
What are they doing?!
Hurry up, Ace's brother!
Navy forces are focusing on Pops now!
This is your only chance
to get beyond the admirals!
Let's break through all
at once! Come with us!
This is a big deal, Straw Hat-boy!
The world's greatest pirate
is putting you to the test!
Huh?
Heehaw!
Whitebeard put all his hopes
on you! That's a big thing!
Are you ready to respond
to his expectations?!
I don't know what Whitebeard wants!
But I came here for...
only one reason, right from the start!
The pirates are gaining vigor!
They're gonna break through!
We need more troops!
Vice Admiral-dono! Let's
get Straw Hat first...!
Wait!
They left Whitebeard alone!
Attack Whitebeard now!
If we can bring Whitebeard
down, we can stop all of them!
They think that they can beat me
if they attack me all at one time!
Whitebeard! Is he invincible?!
Do it, brat!
You just stopped them from
executing Ace on my behalf!
You have the middle initial D,
so show me how the world
will be in years to come!
That's...
Hawk Eye!
Heads up, Straw Hat-boy!
What are you...?!
It's the president's order! We consider
the Navy as our enemy for now! Go!
You're Daz Bones, aren't you?
Straw Hat-boy!
Crocodile!
You're sleeping too much, Mr. 1!
I got out of shape by being in prison.
I don't need you here, Straw Hat! Off you go!
Why are you standing in my way, Crocodile?
I'm not in the best mood now.
So you better watch yourself, Hawk Eye!
Luffy!
I want to help you, too!
Shoot Monkey D. Luffy.
Boa Hancock. Friendly operative. Abort attack.
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?!
You're a Warlord, aren't you, Boa Hancock?!
Why do you keep stopping the Pacifistas?!
I thought you were on the Government's side!
You're such a senseless man!
You don't know anything!
What?!
Let me tell you one thing.
Love is always a hurricane!
What're you talking about?!
The scaffold is close now, Straw Hat-boy!
You just run straight!
Alright!
Now is our chance to do it.
I'm sorry that you must do this when you're
not fully recovered.
But we need you!
It's nothing, Iva-san.
Don't worry about it.
Crab-chan!
What is that?!
Inazuma of the Revolutionary Army! He did it!
There's a bridge! Alright!
Straw Hat is heading straight towards the scaffold!
Do something or he'll reach it!
Don't let him!
We can't! These pirates aren't letting us by!
Gah! Use guns! Fire at Straw Hat!
What?! Th-They are...
commanders of the Whitebeard Pirates!
Ace's brother! Just run straight, don't stop!
Break through all at once!
Don't let him pass through!
Rubber-Rubber...
...Battle Axe!
Luffy-kun, go ahead!
Alright, thanks!
Don't let him go!
Death Wink!
No one will pass by here!
Just advance, Straw Hat-boy!
Straw Hat will make it!
Yeah! Keep going!
Yank Straw Hat down!
Go, Straw Hat!
Set Ace free!
I can't believe that you used that
kid as a trump card, Whitebeard!
But I won't let him go any further!
Whitebeard!
Why don't you stay quiet and watch?
Luffy!
I'm here, Ace!
It's Garp the Hero!
Grandpa! Move out of my way!
I'm not going to move!
Because I'm a vice admiral of the Navy!
I've been fighting against pirates
since long before you were born!
Gramps!
If you wanna pass through here,
you have to kill me first!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Because of the path you two...
have chosen to live!
You gotta find a way, Straw Hat-boy!
Hurry up before the bridge collapses!
Straw Hat!
Luffy-kun!
Ouch!
You bastard!
Grandpa!
Why do you want me to fight with these guys?!
That's your training!
My training?!
It just makes me hungry and I
don't wanna get hit anymore!
Don't be such a baby!
You've got to become the strongest Navy soldier!
I'm gonna become a pirate,
not a Navy soldier!
Huh?
You fool!
Ouch!
Nothing's more painful than Grandpa's fist!
I can't do it, Grandpa! Move out of my way!
If you can't, Ace will die!
No way!
Things don't always go as you want!
I'm not gonna have mercy on you!
Luffy, I consider you...
my enemy!
Garp!
Dammit! What's wrong with me?! This isn't the time to...
Pops, my brother and my crew...
are falling, and yet...
I'm so happy... my tears won't stop...
Even now that it's come
to this... I want to live...
Vice Admiral Garp!
You're their parent after all, Garp.
He is about to get to the scaffold!
You called him a reckless piece of crap!
He is reckless!
I wonder how he will free Fire Fist Ace.
Get lost! You fool!
You're not careful.
Pops!
Take this.
This is the key to your brother's handcuffs.
I have the key!
Luffy, you...
Wh-What the hell is that?!
Look! Fleet Admiral Sengoku is using his power!
I've never seen it before!
You can't get away from me!
Sengoku!
A giant Buddha!
I can't believe that you even have
such a thing, Straw Hat Luffy!
Oh no, the key!
Get ready!
Aim at them and be ready to
fire at a moment's notice!
No way, the key...!
Straw Hat Luffy!
You're a serious criminal who
should be punished by death, too!
I'm gonna execute both of you
brothers with my own bare hands!
What was that? I passed
out all of a sudden...
Straw Hat... Oh!
Three! Why are you here?!
What is that?!
Hey, Three! Protect Ace with a wall!
Rubber-Rubber...
Giant Balloon!
Candle Wall!
Is he expanding?!
The scaffold is collapsing!
What happened?!
Ace is still alive!
We're falling!
I'll make the key! Uncuff him right away!
Alright!
Captain Buggy! There's Brother Three!
What?! What is he doing in
that ridiculous costume?!
I thought he ran away from here already!
Where's the other guy?!
What's taking him so long?!
Since it was such short notice, he's
having trouble getting ready...
Hey, hurry up!
Alright, let's go!
If I tell you that I'm here out
of respect for my late comrade,
are you going to laugh at me?!
No, I won't!
Fire! Blow them away!
Save your brother, Straw Hat!
Okay!
Oh no!
Straw Hat-boy!
No way!
Ace!
Brother Three!
They all got hit!
Fire Fist can't use his power because of
the seastone handcuffs!
He's dead!
And we got Straw Hat, too!
There's a tunnel of fire in the smoke!
You've always been like this!
Luffy!
You've never even listened to me...
and always done such crazy things!
Good!
Oh my!
Ace!
I-I can't believe it!
Straw Hat and Brother Three are alive, too!
Ace!